I want to shout out everybody who got tickets to come see me in Chicago.
Y'all sold out my stand-up show, so I really appreciate that.
There are still tickets available to In The Man That We Trust live.
Listen, you still going to get me.
You still going to get these jokes.
You're going to get a whole other experience because now you're going to get a room full of folks that you're building with.
And we're going to be joined by Damon Williams, a brother in Chicago, who is an organizer, a podcast host, and a brilliant mind.
So we got a lot of dope stuff going on.
If you haven't got tickets yet and you still want to support and you still want to get some of me and your life, why am I so out of breath walking up them stairs?
Then all you got to do is go to AmandaSeals.com and get your tickets.
I will be putting up some other tour dates.
Dallas, Texas.
I'm going to put it up tomorrow.
So look out for that.